I get so bored
From 6:00 to 10:00
From 10:00 to 6:00
From 6:00 to 6:00
All my life
Both day and night
I get so bored
If only
I could find
Alive or dead
A man, a body
An animal
I don't mind
Just to dream
For I get so bored
From 6:00 to 10:00
FAT GIRL
All my life
Both day and night
I get so bored
If only
I could find
Man or woman
A body, a soul
A werewolf
I couldn't care less
Just to dream...
When you fall for a boy,
you try to pin him down too soon.
After three days,
he wants to kick his way free
and get as far away as he can.
Oh, yeah? So let's see
who can pick up a decent boy first.
I'll be generous.
Doesn't even have to be decent.
Any boy.
Even a fat slob like you.
That shows how dumb you are.
You're great physically,
but once they get to know you,
they run a mile.
They run before even
getting to know you!
I'm just too young.
They'd be scared to sleep with me.
But you reek of loose morals.
I don't sleep around.
That's the only thing you don't do.
You have a weird notion
of what "not sleeping around" means.
That's what matters, you know.
I don't think so.
If I meet a man I love,
I'd want to be broken in.
He won't think my first time counts.
The first time should be with nobody.
I don't want a guy bragging
he had me first.
Guys are all sick.
I'm wiped out.
- Oh, come on!
- I thought you wanted a drink.
That place is a dump.
You can sit here if you like.
Tell your friend -
- My sister.
You can't just sit down.
You ask if people mind.
I don't mind.
I asked you to.
Go ahead.
It's very kind of you.
When there's no seats free
and you're thirsty and tired,
it's nice to find someone friendly.
- Fernando.
- Elena.
My little sister, Anais.
Don't just stand there, you lump.
What would you like?
Coffee.
Are you Italian?
- Yes, from Rome.
A banana split - my favorite.
We're on vacation here,
staying at the Residence.
It's nice because it's quiet but...
we can't get out easily.
We're not allowed.
Speak for yourself.
Don't worry.
He can't understand
a word you're saying.
He's just being polite.
No, it's okay.
But can you speak more slowly?
I need to improve my French.
I'm in high school.
I just finished sophomore year.
I'll be a junior next year.
I don't know what I'm gonna do later,
but it's handy, see.
It's part literature,
and part science.
High school.
That was long ago.
I'm in college.
I study law. Avvocato.
You're in college?
That must be different. You're free.
That's the problem.
You're not required
to attend classes,
but you have to take final exams.
You can always retake them in June,
but if you keep falling behind...
Besides,
my father wouldn't understand.
- What does he do?
- My father?
He's an avvocato internazionale.
Mine's a company director.
Excuse me.
I'm finishing my shift.
See you back at the gate.
Been waiting long?
I almost went home.
You're sweet.
- I couldn't believe there was a tornado.
- This is France.
Precisely.
We don't have tornadoes here.
The bed was shaking.
I was terrified.
But I didn't come downstairs to safety.
I pulled the sheets over my head
and decided
to ignore the noise
and go back to sleep.
I must have been crazy.
Sleeping wouldn't save me.
- What?
- What are you studying?
I'm studying law.
Next year I'll be in my third year.
Criminal law?
Yes, that's what interests me.
I think it's much more useful.
Of course, I'll study
international law too
to be a business lawyer.
But l'd like to start out
working for good causes.
So you'll be in international law.
My father insists on it.
He's an international lawyer
and so, of course,
he'd like me to follow
in his footsteps.
Have you gotten acquainted?
ls this okay for you?
- Yes, perfect.
I'm putting him on a diet.
You think I'm fat.
No, but you're not thin for your age.
- Sure you've got enough?
- I was worried it'd all be gone.
And people wonder why she's fat.
It's simple: She eats like a pig.
It's all she does.
It's not her fault - it's hormonal.
She can't help it.
Maybe so,
but she keeps stuffing herself.
It ruins my appetite.
- Oh, come on.
So, how did you meet my daughters?
Francois!
Young people meet.
It just happens these days.
I get so bored
It's not over yet
After my life
and my survival
After my death
I'll still be bored
More than ever before
If only I could find
A specter or a ghost
Woman or man
An animal
I don't mind
To dream...
My lips are soft, huh?
I'm a good kisser.
Yes, you're my love,
but I don't want to marry you yet.
Now that I know men like me,
I want other experiences.
Don't I kiss well?
I've only been kissed once before.
Are you jealous?
I didn't really cheat on you.
Women aren't like bars of soap,
you know.
They don't wear away.
On the contrary,
each lover brings them more,
and you get all the benefit.
You make me sick. How can you
disgust me and attract me so much?
You're the one I'll give it all to.
No, l've never slept
with anyone before.
What are you doing? Can't you ask?
- What are you doing?
- Get lost.
- Going out?
- No, I'm not. How the hell can I?
You didn't invite him here, did you?
Go to sleep.
You hear nothing,
see nothing and know nothing.
No need for makeup
if you're going to sleep.
Go to sleep, okay?
And remember,
mind your own business.
You got the right place.
You said the first door on the left.
My little sister's asleep.
The gateman almost didn't let me in.
- How did you manage?
- I gave him a tip.
Let's put on some music.
We can't.
It's no big deal.
- What's a big deal?
It's as if...
the music counted more than I do.
As if it meant more to you.
I could get offended.
- What?
- Nothing.
I'm sorry
I don't speak French well.
l'd like to tell you
all kinds of things.
That you're so pretty.
I know. It's hard not being able
to understand each other.
To think I could have taken Italian
but chose Spanish instead.
They're machos.
I can try to learn ltalian next year.
No, I have to learn French.
I don't see why.
When I come to see you in Paris,
I'll have learnt French better.
- You'll come to see me in Paris?
- Yes.
I don't actually live in Paris.
I live just outside.
I have a great house, though.
That's okay,
I'll be coming anyway.
You wear your bra to bed?
No, I forgot to take it off.
Can't you help me?
A boy has to work.
If it's too easy,
there's no pleasure.
Don't worry. These things
are always so complicated.
ls that true?
You've loved a lot of girls before?
I'm not the first.
Of course, you're not the first.
I realize that. I'm just asking
if you've had lots and lots of girls.
What does it matter?
I'm here with you now.
But how many have you had?
- Not that many.
- How many?
I don't know.
If you don't know, that means loads.
You're jealous.
I've never had one like you.
Are you sure?
Even if I don't sleep with you
and others do?
That makes a big difference.
I haven't been interested
in a virgin since...
Since?
Since I was 15.
The other girls all slept with you
on the first date?
First or second, it's the same.
No, it's not the same.
You can tell it's all they want.
Sometimes, it's so obvious
it makes me sick.
There was this one once.
She asked me to dinner
and took me to her bedroom.
You're in mine now.
This is different.
We have no choice.
Anyway...
someone told me that this girl
had wanted to go out with me
since the start of the year,
but I hadn't noticed.
So she asks me to dinner,
and we go to her room.
And there we start drinking.
There were four bottles of wine,
just like that, as if by chance.
Four of them.
So we start drinking and eat nothing.
I'm thinking,
"You won't get me, bitch."
I mean, a girl can't take
as much drink as a guy.
So I slow down on my drinking
and keep on filling her glass.
At half past midnight,
I tell her, "Sorry.
Got to go. I'll miss the last tram.
Good night."
I left her blind drunk
and mad at me.
She hasn't spoken to me since.
You didn't like her?
She was kind of cute.
But I got a kick
out of dumping her like that.
Besides, she wasn't the only one.
I've done it loads of times.
It's so easy with girls.
Were you in love
with the others you've slept with?
I know what you're getting at.
You're jealous.
The others don't count.
I only sleep with them
because I'm a guy. That's all.
So if you slept with me,
I'd be like all the other girls?
No.
I'd respect you.
Even if you slept with me?
Yes.
Promise you won't do it.
I don't want you to.
I swear on my mother's head
I'll stay on the edge.
On the edge doesn't count.
- It does.
- lt doesn't.
It does.
Because I count.
You're the only one who counts.
I'm scared you won't
be able to hold back.
Don't worry about that.
That's my problem.
I'm a man. I know if I can
hold back or not. And I can.
But l'd like to have you properly.
That's not possible.
It's dumb if I have to go
with another girl, a girl I don't love.
Will you need to?
Look, I don't want
to bring myself off on my own
in the can. That's sick.
I love you.
I really love you.
But give me time.
I said I don't want to.
I didn't do anything.
I thought you wanted it too.
You're spoiling everything,
understand?
You're spoiling it.
It was fine.
Yes, it was fine.
Don't you realize it was fine?
I can't.
It's not my fault. I can't.
Not like this, straight off.
I didn't trick you.
I warned you.
I'm not a cocktease.
Are you crazy?
How can I resist if you press up
against me like that?
You think I'm some kind of saint?
You can't see
what you're doing to me, huh?
You think it's good for me?
No.
But...
Don't you think it's best
to do it for the first time
with someone who loves you?
Yes.
That would be
a demonstration of love,
a real demonstration of love,
from you to me,
and from me to you too.
I mean, there are loads of guys
who take off
when they see a girl's a virgin.
It's too much hassle,
too much responsibility, see.
They come back
once the job's been done.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's sick.
If not, I'll need to find
another girl older than you.
That's sick too,
and I don't want to do that.
I don't want to.
You're a little girl.
A little girl who looks like a woman.
You have to forgive men.
You're not mad at me?
Are you crazy?
I'm mad about you.
If you were kind...
If I was kind?
All the girls take it the back way.
- All the girls?
- Yes.
That way, it doesn't count.
They can say that
they've never slept with anyone.
- That's sick.
- It isn't.
It's not sick.
It's a demonstration of love.
If you love me the way I love you...
I feel like crying.
No, you mustn't.
You mustn't.
That was a wonderful gift.
Didn't you feel what it did for me?
Yes, but I'm ashamed.
You've shown your love for me.
It was a demonstration of love.
A demonstration of love, see.
From me to you and from you to me.
Do you love me all the same?
Yes.
Don't worry.
You're the kind of girl
that men dream of marrying.
You'd like to marry me?
If you weren't so young, yeah.
I have to take my exams first.
Would you wait for me?
What else am I doing
but waiting for you?
Stay.
Yes.
It's morning.
I have to get back.
You know what I'd like before I go?
I'd like you to take me in your mouth.
Not with my little sister here.
She's asleep.
She might be pretending.
You don't know her.
She's jealous.
She won't accept
that I'm older than her.
She's sleeping, okay?
It would really bother me
if she saw me.
I want to get some sleep!
I'm sick of you rattling on.
- You're awake?
You've been spying on us all night?
No, I've been trying to sleep.
I don't care about you screwing.
You little bitch!
You're calling me a bitch?
That's a good one!
My sister lets some guy
fondle her all night long,
never thinking about me,
and I'm the bitch!
Are you mad at me?
I feel dirty.
I don't feel comfortable.
- Because of my sister?
- No, it's not her.
What should be natural
between two people in love is so -
Well, it's sinister.
I don't want it to happen again, see?
You want to split up?
I want to love you.
Next time.
Next time we'll do it.
You want to? You still want to?
Answer me!
Of course.
If you'd said no, l'd have died.
I'll be your first lover.
The very first.
The one who introduces you to love.
You'll always remember me.
Even with other guys later,
I'll always be the first.
Won't you remember me?
Guys aren't like girls.
You'll never leave me, then.
Stop.
Stop it.
You'll catch cold. Stop it.
No, I'm not cold.
You know what I risk back home
if we're found together?
Tell me.
I'll go to prison.
It's too dangerous. You're not 16.
That's not fair.
It's me who wants it.
See, it wasn't me who stopped first.
Next time,
I'll teach you all about love.
Returned goods?
In the returned goods column!
There's a lot? No difference.
What the hell have you done?
lt was going smoothly,
and once I turn my back...
You want me to come back, huh?
I'm telling you,
that jerk will make me go back.
No, let them get by
on their own for once.
Enjoy your vacation for now.
You think it's easy
to start up a company?
Everything's so sluggish at first
before it takes off.
If you pick the wrong path,
things happen fast.
One asshole and you can go broke.
- Oh, come on.
- It's the old idol with feet of clay.
You're way ahead of the competition.
You feel strong.
And you get done in
by cash flow problems.
Eat. It'll take your mind off things.
- What's Anais doing?
- Showing off.
- Anais!
- Don't shout. I'll get her.
Okay, I was a bit hard on you,
but I had my reasons.
I've just got a temper.
It's not your fault.
I'm sick of being
your ball and chain.
You're not my ball and chain.
But if you're not with me,
they'll never let me out.
They like me to drag you along.
See? You "drag me along."
Yes, tomorrow.
No, the morning's best.
Ah, well, never mind.
Ten past 8:00.
About time!
What's the sense in being here
if we don't eat together?
- What's wrong with her?
- Nothing.
I should hope not!
I'm not working myself to death
to see a face like that on vacation!
In fact, I can't take a vacation,
and I'm the only one not sulking!
Look at you all!
I'm glad you're so happy.
Thank God I'm leaving tomorrow.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with her?
It's adolescence.
She'll get over it.
She'd better get over it fast.
It can't be serious.
You haven't lost your appetite.
Come on, eat.
It'll do you good.
Eating takes your mind off things.
Francois, you almost forgot this.
If he's flying back -
What of it?
We'll go home by car.
I'll drive.
We'll use highway rest stops
when I'm tired.
It'll just take longer.
You'll be driving?
Oh, come on. I can do it.
I just don't like to.
Every year, I wonder
how long your dad will last.
He broke his record this time.
He can't stand vacations.
And he can't stand his partners
being on vacation either.
You'll see. He'll have them
back at work in no time.
I guess I'm not like him.
I understand him.
Vacations suck.
Not again!
You're not getting
the exact same dress as me.
Aren't you sick of copying me?
Try to be original for once.
It's a different color.
It's the same dress.
I'm stuck with you all the time,
and now you copy me.
I didn't know
you chose the same one.
I think it's the best one too.
You could take my boyfriend too
and say, "I didn't see
he was already yours."
He's not yours. He's not a dog.
He is mine. And you're just a bitch,
trying to copy me.
You don't stand a chance.
You'll never be like me.
You must be joking!
I don't want to be like you.
Well you'd better not copy me
in any case.
I didn't realize it was the same one.
Shorter.
I want it shorter.
It's prettier below the knee.
I'm the one wearing it,
and I want it shorter.
Let me do it.
A real mule.
I can't do a thing with her.
It's pretty creepy out here.
I think so, at least.
I feel really uneasy.
You're wrong.
It's great out here.
You can't even see the road.
I hope we lose our way
and never get out,
like in an ancient legend.
Good idea.
I've set my heart to rot away
On the windowsill
I trust in a future day
The crows may come
I hope they will
With their beaks so fleet
They will peck away
At this lump of raw meat
O'er which you thought you held sway
I've set my heart to rot away
On the windowsill
For the joyless joy of the day
My worries fall still
If you see the flock
Of crows fighting o'er it
Throw them not a rock
For I am worth not a bit
I've set my heart to rot away
On the windowsill
I trust in a future day
When the crows come, if they will
With their beaks so fleet
They will peck away
At this lump of raw meat
O'er which you thought you held sway
Slut.
No one would think we're sisters.
It's true.
We don't take after anyone.
It's like we're born of ourselves.
It's funny. We really have
nothing in common. Look at you.
You have small, hard eyes,
while mine are hazy.
But when I look deep into your eyes,
it makes me feel like I belong,
as if they were my eyes.
I feel the same thing.
That's why we're sisters.
When I hate you,
I look at you and then I can't.
It's like hating part of myself.
That's why I loathe you so violently,
because you ought to be like me.
But at times I have the feeling
you're the exact opposite.
I feel that too.
That's why you make me angrier
than anyone else.
I don't let you get away with anything.
You have no rights,
whereas I have a say in your life.
We hate each other
because we're raised as rivals.
It's Dad and Mom's fault.
And yet it's not their fault.
They think it's good,
that it stimulates us.
I think you hated it
when I came along.
I mean,
when I was a baby,
you played mommy with me.
But when I got bigger -
Fatter, you mean!
Bitch.
When I could start belting you
for bossing me around,
when you couldn't play
mommy anymore,
and when I caught up with you
language-wise too.
Really? I don't remember that.
Are you sure
you aren't making it up?
No, I remember it really well.
The day your passion
for educating me ended
was when we were in bed one evening,
in our pink twin beds,
and for some reason you launched
into a speech, bossing me around.
And wham, I pounced on you.
I was pleased because
you called Mom to complain
that l'd pinched you really hard,
and you had two big bruises.
Since that day,
the wind's gone out of your sails.
You've never bossed me around again.
I don't remember that at all.
I remember it perfectly.
I was nice with you.
I'd wheel you in your stroller
and call myself Mommy Lelaine.
- I hated that.
- You did?
You have to admit, it's pretty unfair.
You're allowed to do things
two years sooner than I could.
Yes, I'm not denying that's unfair.
If not, there's no advantage
in being second.
Besides, so many people don't bother
to remember which one's which
since we have the same surname.
I mean, we're not alike.
That's for sure, we're not alike!
Bitch!
I wasn't being mean.
Want me to tell you a secret?
Fernando gave me this.
It's an engagement ring.
A mauve opal.
- He can't have given you that.
You're out of your mind.
There must be a catch.
No. This way, we're engaged now.
It's a pact.
I need to get it fitted.
- When did he give you that?
- In the dunes.
Something's fishy.
I don't think you should have accepted.
It's not right. It's too valuable.
Hold on.
I didn't want some shitty ring!
Where the hell did he get it?
His grandmother left it to him.
I think I'm going
to give myself to him tonight.
You use some really
weird expressions.
If he uses a condom,
I'll let him go all the way.
Spare me the details, please.
You have no idea how scared I am.
Still, I have to go
through it one day.
So it may as well
be with someone I love.
What do you think?
What do you suggest?
In any case, between
what you've already done and that,
there's no moral difference
in my opinion.
There's a world of difference!
Personally, I want my first time
to be with a boy I don't love.
Because afterwards
you realize he doesn't love you
or you don't love him, and you feel dumb.
You'll see when you fall in love.
I doubt it.
In any case, don't mind me.
As long as you don't keep me awake,
you can go at it all night.
Kiss me.
I'm scared.
Be gentle.
- No.
One hard push is best, then it's over.
- No, gently.
- Trust me.
Do audiences come to see you
for kicks or what?
No, not at all.
Why not? Why?
True, my show tackles sexual issues.
There's no sex, that's different.
Maybe I confuse
sex and sexual issues.
It's an investigation
of sexual issues. That's all.
lts a big problem in France.
You have Bardot,
who is a sexual issue.
No, she's a case, not an issue.
She's a case, so she's an issue.
You should read
what De Beauvoir wrote.
She wrote some great things.
I love Bardot,
but she's a sexual issue.
So why do you investigate this issue?
It's a simple and obvious issue
that everyone can understand.
It's a very simple human issue.
And no one is perfect on that level.
Things are more complicated
with other issues,
given the confusion in the world.
How about you?
How do you fall short on that level?
I'm not saying.
She's great, isn't she?
I'll never know the people
I'd like to know. I was born too late.
Excuse me.
Is this the Pingot home?
Come now,
it's not a difficult question.
Still, I suppose it's stupid
to expect an answer.
In that case, I'll come in.
I'm Fernando's mother.
I'm sorry.
I just walked right in.
Are you Elena's mother?
Am I disturbing you.
- Not at all!
The moss grows so fast
with all this wet grass.
This is very awkward, you see.
Very awkward indeed.
No, not at all. Really.
It's an awkward situation.
- Not at all.
- I'm bothering you.
No. I really must compliment you.
Your son is -
It's an awkward situation.
I don't know where to begin.
You know, every summer,
I always bring
a few valuable jewels along.
Some precious,
others just costume jewelry, you see.
I don't check on them every day.
Trouble is, they're memories.
Rings represent the men
whom you managed
to make understand
that they should
offer them to you, you see?
I don't understand.
Besides, it's totally ridiculous
to give such a valuable ring
to some young girl
whom you just happen to meet
on vacation.
It's totally absurd!
What ring? What do you mean?
My mauve opal.
I don't understand how she could have
accepted it just like that.
My son is too young to dispose
of my property. I'm not dead yet!
And I don't intend to die!
I don't understand any of this,
but my daughter's not like that.
There you are.
Where's your sister?
I'm not her keeper.
You're crazy.
You're always ready to back her up
when she screws up, aren't you?
- You're crazy.
- Don't pretend you don't know.
She has a ring
that belongs to this lady.
- Couldn't your son come himself?
- Stop it.
- You're leaving?
- We have to go home one day.
- You didn't stay long.
- That's life.
Can we have some music on?
I didn't do anything.
I get yelled at because of her.
And my vacation's been wrecked.
Your father wants
to have you examined.
How about a police report too?
Published in the papers?
He can't.
- Oh, yes, he can, my girl.
You should have
thought of that first!
I suppose you never had a first time?
Did you ask your dad's permission?
This isn't about me.
I'm sick of it.
Stop this playacting!
I'm sick of you sniveling!
I can't help crying.
Well, cry in silence, then.
Mom.
Stop the car, please.
I feel sick.
Look at the bitch.
She's pleased with herself!
- Shut up.
I hate her.
I wish she'd die.
I don't care.
I'll die with her.
Speak for yourself.
I don't want to die.
No danger of that.
You're not in the dead man's seat.
Turn that down! It's horrible!
I'm driving.
I need to keep myself company.
People are pigs.
Typical French.
We have enough to be ashamed of.
You're eating again?
Mom, that's terrible!
Look who's talking!
I'm worn out.
I need to sleep a bit.
I have to pee.
You think she told dad everything
and that he'll have me examined?
I don't know.
It's sick that people
think it's their business.
It's sick being a virgin.
I'm scared.
He's a real bastard
to have made me think
we were getting engaged.
And with his mother's ring, too.
Stop thinking about it.
Go to sleep.
I can't stop thinking about it.
He was the first.
There'll be plenty of others.
You won't give them
such a hard time now.
Maybe, but I can't stop
thinking about him.
Go to sleep.
He's already forgotten you.
You bitch.
I'm just being honest with you.
You deserve better.
Now go to sleep.
Lock your door.
You're not going to hurt me?
Shut up!
She was in the woods.
She says he didn't rape her.
Don't believe me
if you don't want to.